How to Train Your Dragon: Homecoming is a animation,
fantasy, adventure film directed by Tim Johnson.
It's been ten years since the dragons moved to the Hidden World, and even though Toothless doesn't live in
New Berk anymore, Hiccup continues the holiday traditions he once shared with his best friend.
But the Vikings of New Berk were beginning to forget
about their friendship with dragons.
Hiccup, Astrid, and Gobber know just what to do to keep
the dragons in the villagers' hearts.
And across the sea, the dragons have a plan of their own...
Hiccup (voice), played by Jay Baruchel.
Astrid (voice), played by America Ferrera.
Gobber (voice), played by Craig Ferguson.
Zephyr (voice), played by Madalyn Gonzalez.
Fishlegs (voice), played by Christopher Mintz-Plasse.
Nuffink (voice), played by Liam Ferguson.
How to Train Your Dragon: Homecoming is a 2019 animated short
film by DreamWorks and directed by Tim Johnson.
Set before the epilogue of How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World (2019), it was
simultaneously released  on DVD and aired on NBC on December 3, 2019.